<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foreword on Spider Docs</title>
    <link>mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foreword on Spider Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 12:05:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Reference</title>
      <link>mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/quick-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:26:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/quick-reference/</guid>
      <description>The Jumping Spider Disco Floor is a system that creates a temperature differential between spiders during experiments observing their mating habits.
Features  Position Tracking - Automatically record movements of spiders and other small subjects. Temperature Monitoring - Record relative temperatures of test subjects. Selective Heating - Heat one spider up by a specified differential. Thermal and Visible Video Recording - Review spider movements for context. Adjustable Detection Parameters - Tune the instrument for use with other subjects and in different conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Manual</title>
      <link>mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/user-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 12:28:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>mikewillems.github.io/spider-disco/user-manual/</guid>
      <description>
hugo new &amp;lt;user-manual&amp;gt;/filename.md  This Document will be eventurally updated to contain all of the Spider Disco project notes and enable troubleshooting and hacking of the system.
 Goals  position / movement temperature  Research Findings  absorption spectra power calculations spider tolerance laser options eye safety &amp;amp; regulation  Hardware  system diagram laser system galvo system visible spectrum camera infrared spectrum camera PC enclosure RPi extensibility considered options  Software  system diagram drivers front end tracking control video interface considered options  Interface  user flow  each step  getting and using data considerations  Troubleshooting  expected versus unexpected behavior (and failsafe) cameras &amp;amp; alignment PC issues  running out of memory something pauses avoiding linux updates  laser issues steering issues   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>